Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - B
    - Bobroff, Allen, Educational Psychology, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Boehm (Boehn), Susan, Nursing, 1991, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Boersma, Wendell C., Bureau of School Services, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Boettner, Donald, Environmental and Industrial Health, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Boettner, Edward, Industrial Health, 1963, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Boggins, Kevin, Classical Studies, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Bogusky, Rachel, Education, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Bolcom, William E., Music, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Boldt, Warren, Housing, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Bole, Giles, Medical School, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Bolgar, Vera (Box 2)
    - Bolt, Jay A., Mechanical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bolton, Dale L., Education, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Boman, Dean O., Business Administration, 1971, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Bommersbach, Jana, UM News Office, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Bond, Floyd A., Business Administration, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bonk, Wallace J., Library Sciences, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Bonn, Richard, Higher Education (Box 2)
    - Bonus, Ted, State and Community Relations, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Borchardt, Jack, Civil Engineering, 1970, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bordin, Edward S., Bureau of Psychological Services; Psychology, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Bordua, David J., Sociology, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Borer, Katarina, Physical Education, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Borgsdorf, Charles, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Borkin, Harold J., Architecture, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bornstein, George, English, 1993, 1986, 1991, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Bornstein, Morris, Economics, 1962, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Bossart, Eugene R., Vocal Literature and Accompanying, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Bostian, David W., Inst. In Psychiatry, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Boston, Orlan W., Metal Processing, 1947 (Box 2)
    - Bott, Raoul, Mathematics, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Bouchard, Harry, 1952 (Box 2)
      (na 136)
    - Bouchard, Vincent E., Hospital Pharmacy (Box 2)
    - Boufford, F. W., Naval Science, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Bouland, Peter, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Boulding, Kenneth, Economics; Center for Study on Conflict Resolution, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Boutwell, Frederick K., Mechanical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bouxsein, Alec P., Institute of Public Policy Studies, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Bowditch, John, History, 1962, 1976, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Bowen, Ella, Occupational Education, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Bower, James R., University School; Education; Admissions, 1961, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Bowers, David G., CRUSK, 1962, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Bowman, Robert, Health Education, 1963, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Boyce, Earnest, Engineering; Public Healthl; Municipal and Sanitary Engineering, 1959, 1951, 1983, 1978 (Box 2)
      (na 138)
    - Boyd (Box 2)
      (na 139)
    - Boyd, Florence I., Registration and Records, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Boyd, Joseph A., Institute of Science and Technology, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Boyd, Julian C., English Language Institute, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Boyd, Robert A., UMRI, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Boylan, Paul C., Music, 1990, 1976, 1972, 1993, 1971, 1979, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Boyle, Bill, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Boyle, James, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Boyle, Thomas A., 1955 (Box 2)
      (na 141)
    - Boys, Richard C., English, 1962, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Brabec, Michael, Public Health, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Brablec, Carl, Regent, 1964, 1962, 1965 (Box 2)
      (nb 117-118)
    - Brace, William (Box 2)
    - Bracey, Robert, Music, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Brackenbury, Robert L., 1949 (Box 2)
      (na 146-147)
    - Brackett, Robert D., English, College of Engineering (Box 2)
    - Brackett, Robert D., Jr., Extension Program; Natural Resources (Box 2)
    - Bradetich, Jeffrey, Music, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bradley, Hugh, Industrial Engineering, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Bragado, Maximo, Music, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Bragg, Edward M., Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 2)
    - Brahce, Carl, Education, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Brake, Mary, Nuclear Engineering, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Brandon, Arthur L., 1952 (Box 2)
    - Brandon, Mrs. Arthur L., 1947 (Box 2)
      (na 157-159)
    - Brandt, Carl G., English, College of Engineering; Speech, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Brandt, Richard B., Philosophy, 1979, 1978, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Brasch, Jerome, Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Brashers, Howard, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Brater, Ernest, Hydraulic Engineering, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Brauer, Richard D., 1949 (Box 2)
      (na 161-162)
    - Braun, Frank X., German, 1950 (Box 2)
    - Braun, George, Business Administration, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Brauneck, Rita, Admissions, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Brazer, Harvey E., Economics, 1978, 1959, 1957, 1977 (Box 2)
      (na 163)
    - Brazer, Marjorie, Graduate School, 1977, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Breakstone, Mark, Student, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Breitenbach, Jerome, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Bremer, Roy, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Bretsch, Howard S., Education, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Bretton, Henry L., 1962 (Box 2)
      (nb 127)
    - Brewer, Garry, Natural Resources, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Briant, Peter C., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 2)
      (nb 128)
    - Bridges, Betty, 1951 (Box 2)
      (na 165)
    - Bridges, Lynn, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Bridges, Robert, 1930 (Box 2)
    - Brier, John C., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1961 (Box 2)
      (nb 129)
    - Brierly, James W., 1948 (Box 2)
      (na 167-171)
    - Briggs, Clyde, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Briggs, Dale E., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1961, 1978, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Briggs, Louis I., Goelogy, 1962, 1975, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Briggs, Robert P., Regent, 1949, 1967 (Box 2)
      (na 173-174)
    - Brigham, George B., Jr., Architecture, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Brink, Carol, Nursing (Box 2)
    - Brinkerhoff, James F., Vice President and Chief Financial Officer; Plant Department, 1967, 1976, 1977-1982, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Brinkerhoff, Margaret (Box 2)
    - Brinkman, Joseph, Piano, 1960 (Box 2)
      (na 176)
    - Bristol, Denise L., Minority Program, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Britton, Allen, School of Music, 1970, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Britton, W. Earl, English, College of Engineering, 1960, 1968 (Box 2)
      (na 177)
    - Brockway, Lawrence, Chemistry, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Brody, Gerald, Pathology, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Brogan, Donna, Public Health, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Bromage, Arthur, Political Science, 1956, 1966, 1972, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Bromage, Mary C., Written Communications, 1961, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Brooks, NROTC, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Brophy, David J., Business Administration, 1967, 1994, 1986, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Browder, Olin L., Jr., Law, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Brower, Robert H., Far Eastern Languages, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Camilla A., University Relations, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Deming B., Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1960, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Dennis, WUOM, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Diane, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Donald, Environmental Health; Natural Resources, 1985, 1977, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Donald R., Pyschology, 1979, 1973, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Dugald E. S., Zoology, 1960, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Frances, Extension Service, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Brown, George Granger, Chemical Engineering, 1952, 1949 (Box 2)
      (na 179, nb 133)
    - Brown, Gerald S., History, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Gordon C., Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Brown, H. Douglas, English Language Institute, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Julius, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Laura Sky, Information Services, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Linz, Regional Director, Dearborn, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Marilyn Mason, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Morton B., Public Health, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Paul, Regent, 1970, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Paul L., University Publications, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Rex V., 1970 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Richard K., Electrical Engineering, 1955, 1978, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Browne, Richmond, Music, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Brownell, Herbert, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Brownell, Lloyd E. (Box 2)
    - Browning, Horace K., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Brownson, Jacques, Architecture, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bruden, William, Museum of Zoology, 1954 (Box 2)
      (na 185)
    - Bruggeman, Teresa, Physiology, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Brummet, R. Lee, Business Administration, 1959, 1960 (Box 2)
      (na 189)
    - Bruneau, Glenn P., Natural Resources, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bruno, Glenn (Box 2)
      (na 190)
    - Brunskill, Philip J., Alumni Association, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Bryan, Keith, Music, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bryan, Wright, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Bryant, Bunyan, Natural Resources, 1996, 1995, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Bryant, Dale, Architecture, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Buck, James, Industrial Engineering, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Buck, Lucile, Community Health Services, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Budidjaja, Robert, Housing EOM, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Buehl, Louis, Naval Science, 1965, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Buhl, Walter, Management, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bulbick, Walter, Purchasing, 1962 (Box 2)
      (na 191)
    - Bulkley, Jonathan, Natural Resources, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Bull, Hempstead S., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bullmer, Kenneth, Admissions, Flint College, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Bulloch, James, Accounting, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Bunch, Howard M., HSRI, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Bundra, Francis, Music, 1978, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bundra, Frank, Music, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Buning, Harm, Aeronautical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bunting, Dean, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Burbank, Jane, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Burch, John, Zoology; Museum of Zoology, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Burckhalter, Joseph H., Pharmaceutical Chemistry, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Burke, Daniel, Canterbury House, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Burke, Evelyn, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Burklund, Carl E., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Burks, Arthur W., Philosophy; Communication Sciences; Computer and Communication Sciences, 1952, 1964, 1968, 1974 (Box 2)
      (na 193)
    - Burns, Charles, Radiological Health, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Burns, Laurie, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Burns, Thelma, Housing EOM, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Burris, Richard W., Investment Office; Attorney's Office, 1959, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Burrows, Edwin G., Broadcasting Service, 1949, 1958 (Box 2)
      (na 195)
    - Bursley, Gilbert E., Development Council (Box 2)
    - Bursley, Joseph A., 1947, 1950 (Box 2)
      (na 200-205)
    - Bursly, Philip, 1953 (Box 2)
      (na 207)
    - Burt, William, Zoology, 1952, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Buss, David, Psychology, 1989, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Butera, Donald N., Accounting, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Butler, Thomas W., Jr., Electrical Engineering, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Butman, Jean, Institute for Social Research, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Butter, Irene H., Hospital Administration, 1990 (Box 2)
    - Buttrey, Theodore, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Butts, Thomas, Orientation; VP Academic Affairs; Financial Aid, 1969, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Buxton, Sally, Commission on Women, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Byers, Ruth, 1956 (Box 2)
      (na 206)
    - Bykowski, Justine, Institute of Gerontology, 1973, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Byrd, Clarence, Business Administration, 1965 (Box 2)
      (nb 140)
    - Byrn, Delmont K., Education, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Byrne, Don, 1955 (Box 2)
  - C
    - Cacioppo, George, Music, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Caddell, Robert M., Mechanical Engineering, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Cain, Albert, Psychology and Psychiatry, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Cain, Louise G., Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Cain, Stanley A., 1950 (Box 2)
    - Calahan, Donald A., Electrical Engineering, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Calder, H. B., Education, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Calhoon, Floyd N., Mechanical Engineering, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Calhoun, Hazel, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Callnin, Donald A., Laundry (Box 2)
    - Calohan, Donald, Electrical Engineering, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Cambon, G. Glauco, Italian and English, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Cameron, George C., Near Eastern Cultures, 1949, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Cameron, Howard, Greek and Latin; Museum of Zoology, 1967, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Campbell, Angus, ISR, 1976, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Campbell, Jean, CEW, 1985, 1967, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Campbell, John, Political Science (Box 2)
    - Canale, Raymond P., Civil Engineering, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Canham, Donald B., Physical Education and Athletics (Box 2)
    - Cannell, Charles F., Psychology in Journalism; Survey Research Center, 1961, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, Delores, Admissions, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, Joseph H. (Box 2)
      (na 218)
    - Cant, Nell, Physiology, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Cantor, Nancy, Psychology, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Cantrall, Irving J., Zoology, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Carduner, Jean R., French, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Cares, Charles W., Jr., Landscape Architecture, 1964, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Carey, Chris, News Service, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Carey, John J., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Carey, William, Business Administration, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Carignan, George R., Electrical Engineering, 1969, 1964, 1962, 1989, 1985, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Carlisle, Arthur, Business Administration, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Carlson, Raymond, Accounting, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Carlson, William, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Carman, James M., Business Administration, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Carnahan, Brice, Biostatistics; Chemical Engineering, 1963, 1988, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Carnes, John, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Carow, John, Forest Management, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Clyde A., Music, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Eugenia, Pharmacology, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Finley, Education, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, John, Nuclear Engineering, 1973, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, John B., Extension Service, 1965, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Kurt, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Carpenter, Robert, Architecture, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Carr, Arthur, English, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Carr, John III, Math, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Carr, Lowell, 1950 (Box 2)
    - Carr, Robert I., Civil Engineering, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Carrick, Leo L., Chemical Engineering, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Carroll, Mary Ann, Engineering, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Carroll, Raymond E., Engineering, Continuing Engin. Ed.; Engineering Placement, 1960, 1975, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Carrothers, George E., Education, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Carruth, Hayden K., Speech, 1957, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Carson, Dan, Psychology; Mental Health Research Institute, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Carter, Beryl L., Social Work (Box 3)
    - Carter, George R., Jr., Personnel Administration, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Carter, Paul D., Education, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Carter, Richard, 1989, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Carter, William, Architecture and Design, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Cartwright, Dorwin, Psychology, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Carvalho, Gerard F., Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Carver, Harry C., Mathematics, 1954 (Box 3)
    - Case, Ava C., Piano, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Case, Francis, Senator, 1953, 1954 (Box 3)
      (na 237-238)
    - Case, Kenneth, Physics, 1965, 1955 (Box 3)
    - Case, Lee O., Chemistry, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Cash, William, Jr., Human Relations, 1969, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Caskey, Clark C., Bureau of Industrial Relations; Business Administration, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Cassara, Frank, Architecture and Design, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Castiglionia, Niccilo, Music, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Catford, John, English Language Institute; Linguistics, 1964, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Cather, James N., Zoology, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Cave, William, Education, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Cavender, George R., School of Music, 1969, 1972, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Cawley, Janet, News Service, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Cesari, Lamberto, Mathematics, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Chaffers, James, Architecture, 1975, 1982, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Chaffin, Don, Industrial Engineering, 1972, 1991, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Chakrovot, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Chambers, David L., Law, 1979, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Chambers, Merritt M., Higher Education (Box 3)
    - Chambers, Ross, Romance Languages, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Chambers, Walter, Landscape Architecture, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Chan, Shu-Gar, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chan, Shu-Yun, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chandler, David C., Zoology, 1962, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Chapin, Chester F., English, College of Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chapman, E. Thomas, Political Science, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Chapman, Sydney, Institute of Science and Technology, 1959 (Box 3)
      (na 249)
    - Charbeneau, Gerald, Dentistry, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Charlton, Richard E., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chartell, 1955 (Box 3)
      (na 250, nb 173)
    - Chase, Geraldine, History, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Chase, Warren W., Wildlife Management, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Chastain, Clark, IST, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Chatman, Stephen, Music, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Chavarria-Aguilar, Oscar L., English Language Institute; English, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Chavis, John, History, 1968, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Chesler, Mark, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Child, Charles G., III, Surgery, 1959, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Chilman, Kenneth, Natural Resources, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Chong, Hun (Box 3)
    - Chopp, Marjorie, English Language Institute, 1958 (Box 3)
      (na 253)
    - Christen, Jerold, Capt. USAF, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Christensen, Halvor N., Biological Chemistry, 1959, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Christian, Palmer, UM Interior Decorator, 1952 (Box 3)
    - Christman, Luther, Nursing; Institute for Social Research, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Chu, Chiao-Min, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chuang, Kuei, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Chudacoff, Edward, Music, 1965, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Chupp, Timothy, Physics, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Church, Michael P., Extension Service; Art, 1949, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Churchill, Paul, Physiology, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Churchill, Ruel V., Mathematics, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Churchill, Stuart W., Chemical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Cianciola, Frank J., Michigan Union, 1987, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Cirre, Manuela M., Spanish, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Cisney, Marcella (Box 3)
    - Clancy, John, Speech, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Clark, John, Mechanical Engineering, 1965, 1975, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Clark, Lou, Extension Service, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Clark, Samuel K., Engineering Mechanics, 1959, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Clarke, A. Bruce, Mathematics, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Clarke, Peter, Journalism, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Clarke, Robert, Business Administration, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Clarkson, James D., Geography, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Claude, Inis L., Jr., Political Science, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Clausen, Aage, Institute for Social Research, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Clauss, Joan, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Clay, Margaret, Psychology; Mental Health Research Institute, 1964, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Clemence, Roger, Architecture, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Clifford, Beverley C., Survey Research Center, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Clifford, Robert, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Cloke, Paul L., Geology, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Coats, Keith H., Chemical Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Cobb, Janice, Broadcasting Service, 1954, 1950 (Box 3)
    - Cobb, Sidney, Survey Research Center; Public Health, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Cochran, Kenneth, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cocks, J. Fraser III, Michigan Historical Collections, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cogswell, Jim, Art, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Albert, Music, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Bennett, Physiology, 1963, 1980, 1975, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Carl, Philosophy, 1974, 1966, 1979, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Hubert, Humanities, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Julius, Institute for Study on Mental Retardation, 1971, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Malcolm, ILIR, 1977, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Milton J., Art, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Stuart B., Naval Architecture, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Cohen, Wilber J., School of Social Work; School of Education, 1969, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cohn, James, Mathematics, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cohn, Thomas S., Psychology; Sociology, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Colby, Howard R., Mechanical Engineering, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Colby, Lila, Sea Grant, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cole, Alan, Meterology, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cole, David E., Mechanical Engineering, 1993, 1981, 1978, 1977, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cole, Elsa (Box 3)
    - Cole, Robert, Engineering Drawing, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cole, Robert, Center for Japanese Studies, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Cole, William, Music, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Coleman, Michael, Office of Academic Affairs, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Coles, William, English, 1964, 1968, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Collins, Morgan, Business Administration, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Collins, Walter, Men's Glee Club, 1955 (Box 3)
    - Collver, Andrew, Sociology, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Colombo, Louis J., Jr., Major Gifts Committee, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Colwell, Lester V., Mechanical Engineering, 1960, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Comninou, Maria, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Conard, Alfred F., Law, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Conklin, James L., Anatomy (Box 3)
    - Conlon, Emerson W., 1946, 1950 (Box 3)
      (na 286-na 287)
    - Conn, Jerome W., Internal Medicine, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Connellan, Thomas, Bureau of Industrial Relations (Box 3)
    - Conners, Edward J., Hospital Administration, 1960 (Box 3)
      (nb 192)
    - Connors, Edward J. (Box 3)
    - Conquergood, Colleen, LSA, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Conrey, Lawrence, Education, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Consani, Joseph, Epidemiology, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Converse, Philip E., Survey Research Center, 1958, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Cook, Constance, Assistant to the President, 1990, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Cook, Warren, Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cooley, Keith W., Engineering, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Coombs, Clyde H., Psychology, 1959, 1979, 1977, 1972, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Coon, Minor J., Biological Chemistry, 1959, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Coons, Dorothy, Institute of Gerontology, 1985, 1972, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Bernice, Physical Education, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Charles, Conservation, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Dan H., Educational Administration, 1964, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Frank E., Law, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, K. Paul, Music, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Cooper, Lewis H., Music, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Cooperrider, Luke K., Law, 1953 (Box 3)
    - Cope, Robert, Extension Service, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Copeland, Arthur H., Mathematics, 1964 (Box 3)
      (na 314)
    - Copeland, Richard F., Chemistry, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Copi, Irving M., Philosophy, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Copley, Frank O., Latin, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Coppola, Brian, Chemistry, 1999, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Corey, Clark, 1954 (Box 3)
      (na 319)
    - Cork, James M., Physics, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Cornelius, Paul, Engineering English, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Cornell, John B., 1954 (Box 3)
      (na 323)
    - Cornell, Richard G., Biostatistics, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Cornish, Herbert, Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Correll, Gene, BIR, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Correll, Richard, 1948 (Box 3)
      (na 324)
    - Corse, Leslie, Center for Population Planning, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Cortright, Donald N., Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Corwell, George, Natural Resources, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Cosovich, Jon, VP Development and Community Relations, 1994, 1986, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Costabile, Jane, Social Work, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Costello, Cathleen, Career Planning and Placement, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Costello, James D., Architecture, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Costin, Dean, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Cottrell, Corrine, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Cottrell, Howard R., Staff Benefits, 1959, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Couch, Richard B., Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1960, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Counsell, Raymond, Pharmacy, 1976, 1970, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Courant, Paul, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Courte, Robert, Music, 1959, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Cowan, Archibald, Natural Resources, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Cowan, Donald R. G., Marketing, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Cowden, Roy W., 1949 (Box 3)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, English (Box 3)
    - Cox, Judy, Housing Info., 1985, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Coyne, George H., Business Office, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Crafton, L. Joseph, Business and Government, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Craig, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Craig, Cecil, Mathematics, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Craig, Esther, Naval Science, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Craine, Lyle E., Conservation, 1959 (Box 3)